# Aruna Duraisamy

#### Web Developer

Web developer with 5 years of experience in Microsoft full stack web development and 2 years of experience in Front-End development. A Self-motivated team player, good in diagnostics, with a passion for solving problems and a thirst for learning.

aruna.durai.official@gmail.com

Norwich, United Kingdom

07459957809

in linkedin.com/in/aruna-duraisamy

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# Senior Front-end Developer TALKTALK PORTAL

12/2012 - 09/2014

Responsibilities:

- PHP, Zend Framework, MVC, XHTML, CSS 3, jQuery, MySQL.
- Worked closely with Product owner and Design Team at onshore, in understanding the requirements and implementation.
- Trained fellow developers in Front-end development.

#### Developer

#### FLYPP DEVELOPER PORTAL

11/2009 - 12/2011

Responsibilities:

- A Developer Portal, targeted for Developers to submit their mobile applications.
- SharePoint 2007, ASP.NET 3.5, C#, SQL Server 2008 and Windows Server 2008.
- Involved in Development, Testing, Live deployment and Support.

#### Developer

#### **GIFTS AND ENTERTAINMENT**

10/2009 - 11/2009

Responsibilities

- A web application targeted for the employees of British Giant Company to capture the gifts and Government hosting information.
- ASP.NET 2.0, C#, MS SQL Server 2000, Telerik Radajax, Aspose tools.
- Involved in Development and Testing.

#### Developer

#### **EUROPEAN RESELLER SYSTEM**

10/2007 - 10/2009

Responsibilities

- Web application targeting PAN European Resellers with multi-lingual support, which allows Resellers to place orders and manage Reseller and Sub-Resellers.
- ASP.NET, C#, VB.NET, Window services, SQL Server.
- Involved in Development and Testing.

### **SKILLS**



# **EDUCATION**

# Bachelor of Engineering (Computer Science) JJ COLLEGE OF ENGINEERING, TRICHY, TAMIL NADU, INDIA

08/2004 - 04/2007

Gold Medalist

## **CERTIFICATIONS**

Microsoft Certified Professional - Programming in HTML5 with JavaScript and CSS3 09/2017

Microsoft Azure Fundamentals (AZ-900) 02/2021

#### **ORGANIZATIONS**

Infosys Technologies Limited (07/2007 - 09/2014)

\*Gap in employment\* (09/2014 - Present)

Took a purposeful 7 year break from employment to raise a family and now ready to leverage my Web Development skills.